As of January 1st, 2020, many governments worldwide require manufacturers and subsequent
distributors of lithium cells or batteries, and products powered by lithium cells or batteries,
to make available a battery testing summary.
This battery testing summary requirement is most commonly known as UN38.3, and applies
to all lithium batteries and cells manufactured after June 30th, 2003.
To be compliant with this standard, all selling partners must provide a test summary for any
lithium cells or batteries or products powered by lithium cells or batteries.
Test summaries are required to confirm that lithium batteries meet UN38.3 testing requirements.
Failure to provide this information can result in regulatory enforcement or other actions.
For more information about the UN38.3 test summary requirements and how to upload the
test document, please visit Amazon Help pages in Seller Central and Vendor Central.
Thank you for partnering with us to maintain a safe, compliant marketplace for lithium
cells and batteries.